Contactar

japp19961996@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/japp1996 (LinkedIn)

Aptitudes principales

Laravel

Vue.js

Hojas de estilos en cascada (CSS)

Jose Angel Padron

Web developer of LimonByte

Aragua Area, Venezuela

Extracto

Web developer of limonbyte. Specialized in web application development, API and graphic design.

I have worked on approximately 7 web projects and I am currently continuing to develop.

I am training me with courses of platzi.com Actually I am learning python because i want to learn artificial intelligence

Experiencia

LimonByte Web Developer septiembre de 2018 - Present Aragua, Venezuela

Work on project based in POO.

Frameworks: Laravel, Angular 1 and Vue.js

SGDB: Mysql

Librerías: Materializecss, Jquery

www.metalesaleados.com
Technical Support Analyst
mayo de 2018 - agosto de 2018 (4 meses)

Turmero, Edo. Aragua

Computer technical support.

Tabin, C.A.
Web Developer
enero de 2018 - mayo de 2018 (5 meses)
Venezuela

Work on project based in Structured programming.

Programming Languages :PHP and Javascript

SGDB: Mysql

Librerías: Jquery and Bootstrap.

Agrolucha, C.A. Internship septiembre de 2013 - julio de 2016 (2 años 11 meses) Aragua, Venezuela

File Management, Files, petty cash, purchase orders.

Management of the administrative system and nomina profit plus Modules: Purchases, Sales, Inventory, Maintenance, Reports.

Basic handling of Windows Server 2003-2008

Computer technical support

Support in reception, dispatch and inventory of items in storage

Educación

Universidad Politécnica Territorial del Estado Aragua "Federico Brito Figueroa"

Tecnicatura, Técnico superior en Informática · (2016 - 2018)